Blake Yeboah

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Profile

I am a **full stack software developer** who loves to build applications from static websites to social networks. I utilize a variety of languages and frameworks to build effective web solutions for business's and their clients. My preferred tech stack is the **MERN stack**. I love learning and am always open to learning new technologies to get the job done.

Projects

DevNetwork

A full stack web application with authentication, post functionality, messaging functionality and more built on the MERN stack. In other words, this web app is a social network for developers to share their projects and socialize with other developers.

Code - Preview

Career Busters

A responsive website for a future business called career busters that has a great user experience (UX) designed to engage users. It has animations, clean transitions and a great UI that emphasizes the branding of the business.

Code - Preview

Audi Re-Design

A redesign of Audi Centre Brisbane's current website that is responsive and looks great on all devices. Built with HTML, CSS, Sass and JavaScript. This project displays all of Audi's car models in a presentable, effective way.

Code - Preview

Education

Self Taught

OCTOBER 2018 - PRESENT

I taught myself web development through online resources like Udemy and YouTube as well as browsing documentation .

Experience

Work Experience, Digital8

SEPTEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

During my 1 week work experience at Digital8, i learned a lot from developers in a professional environment that has helped me improve as a developer and expand my knowledge base.

Developing Web Applications, Personal

JANUARY 2018 - PRESENT

I've been programming personal web applications since 2018 and have progressed significantly as a developer.

Details

Brisbane, Australia 0412899465 blakekyeboah@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Australian

Links

Portfolio

Github

LinkedIn

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Sass (Pre-processor)

React

MobX (State Management)

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

Git & Github

Typescript

Languages

English

References

References available upon request